sbcounty.gov 2011-05-23

# County of San Bernardino, California - Official Web Site

 |  |  |   
---|---  
  **WELCOME TO THE COUNTY OF SAN BERNARDINO** | 

|  |  | Board of Supervisors |  |  |   | County  
Vision|  |  |  | Open Government |  |  |  | Visiting |  |  |  | Working |  |  |  | Contacts  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
_**Privacy Policy**_  
---  
  
**Welcome**  
Thank you for visiting the San Bernardino County website. This website is designed to make it easier and more efficient for San Bernardino County citizens and businesses to interact with their local government. Like all online resources, we recognize that visitors to this website are concerned about their privacy. San Bernardino County is committed to preserving your privacy when visiting this website. 

This policy describes the County's privacy practices regarding information collected from visitors to this website. This policy describes what data is collected and how that information is used. The County may, at its sole discretion, change, modify, add, or delete portions of this policy. Because this privacy policy applies only to this website, you may wish to examine the privacy policy of any website, including other local websites you access through this website. 

**Information Collected When You Visit this Website**  
When visiting this website the County automatically collects and stores the following information about your visit: 

  * The Internet Protocol address and domain name of your Internet service provider. The Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer, which can be used to direct internet traffic to you; 
  * The type of browser and operating system you used; 
  * The date and time you visited this site; 
  * The web pages or services you accessed at this site; and 
  * The URL or web site address of the web site you visited prior to coming to this website and from which any web page on this site was linked.

This information is used to improve this website's content and to help the County understand how people are using this website. This information is collected for statistical analysis, to determine what information is of most and of least interest to our visitors, and to identify system performance or problem areas. The information is not collected for commercial marketing purposes and the County does not sell or distribute the information collected from the portal for commercial marketing purposes. 

**Information Collected When You Email this Website**  
If during your visit to this website you send an email to the County, your email address and the contents of your email will be collected. 

The information collected is not limited to text characters and may include audio, video, and graphic information formats you send us. 

Your email address and the information contained in your email may be used to respond to you, to address issues you identify, to further improve this website, or to forward your email to another agency for appropriate action. Your email address is not collected for commercial marketing purposes and the County does not sell or distribute your email address for commercial marketing purposes. 

**Personal Information and Choice**  
"Personal information" is information about an individual, for example, an individual's name, address, and phone number. A domain name or Internet Protocol address is not considered personal information. 

Personal information is not collected through this website unless you send an email or complete a web based form containing such information to the County through this website. If you do not communicate with this website it does not affect your ability to use any other features of this website or other government websites. 

The County does not knowingly collect personal information from children or create profiles of children through this website. People are cautioned that the collection of personal information provided by any individual in an email or web based form will be treated the same as information given by an adult, and may, if not protected by federal or State law, be subject to public access. The County encourages parents and teachers to be involved in children's Internet activities and guide the children whenever children are asked to provide personal information online. 

**Disclosure of Information Collected Through This Website**  
Information collected through this website, personal or otherwise, may, if not protected by local, federal or state law, be subject to disclosure pursuant to law, such as the [Freedom of Information Act (FOIA)](http://www.archives.gov/foia/), or court order. 

Additionally, the County may disclose personal information to local, federal or state law enforcement authorities to enforce its rights against unauthorized access or attempted unauthorized access to the County's information. 

**Security**  
The information contained in this policy should not be construed in any way as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof the security of information provided via this website. For site security purposes and to ensure that this website remains available to all users, the County employs software to monitor traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause damage to this website. 

**Links Disclaimer**  
In order to provide visitors with certain information, this website may provide links to local, state and federal government agencies, and websites of other organizations. A link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, viewpoint, accuracy, opinions, policies, products, services, or accessibility of that website. Once you link to another website from this website, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that website.

**Information Disclaimer**  
Information provided on this website is intended to allow the public immediate access to public information. While all attempts are made to provide accurate, current, and reliable information, the County recognizes the possibility of human and/or mechanical error. Therefore, the County, its employees, officers and agencies make no representations as to the accuracy, completeness or suitability of the information provided by this website, and deny any expressed or implied warranty as to the same. The County reserves the right to make changes at any time and without notice, and assumes no liability for damages incurred directly or indirectly as a result of errors, omissions or discrepancies. 

**Contact Information**  
For questions regarding this Privacy Policy please contact **[webmaster@sbcounty.gov](mailto:webmaster@sbcounty.gov)**

County Home Page  

| 

**Yucaipa Branch Library Grand Re-Opening**  
Ribbon cutting and refreshments.  
**[_Click here_](http://www.sbcounty.gov/library/home/)** for details.  
  
---  
**Rialto Branch Library Grand Re-opening and Expansion**  
Ribbon cutting and refreshments.  
**[_Click here_](http://www.sbcounty.gov/library/home/)** for details.  
  
**Free Cancer Awareness & Screening**  
ARMC Outpatient Care Center event  
**[_Click here_](http://www.sbcounty.gov/Uploads/CAO/Calendar/Content/1CancerSem2011.pdf)** for details.  
  
**County Museum Summer Day Camps 2011**  
Several sessions June to July.  
**[_Click here_](http://www.sbcounty.gov/museum/pdf/summerdaycamp2011.pdf)** for details.  
  
**JDRF Annual Car Show**  
Cucamonga-Guasti Regional Park  
**[_Click here_](http://www.sbcounty.gov/Uploads/CAO/Calendar/Content/JDRF_2011_Guasti_Car_Show.pdf)** for details.  
  
**Arrowhead Regional Medical Center**  
Health & Safety Fair from 10 a.m.- 2 p.m.  
**[_Click here_](http://www.sbcounty.gov/uploads/cao/calendar/content/health_fair_2011save_the_date_digital_flyer.png)** for details.  
  
  |   RSS - Upcoming Events
